This is the golden classic "The brother who overcomes all thorns".
This program is on
Exclusively on MangoTV app
Hello everyone, I am Thieu Minh Minh
Junior high school
Autumn travel of teenagers and Taiwanese people
Start immediately
We have four Taiwan native classmates
Everyone wants to be a tour guide in Dai Loan area
In the end, who will become the final card guide?
Don't say much more
Let's invite four post-selection people to the stage
Older brother
Hello brother
I am the class leader of today's tour guide class
I am Thieu Minh Minh
Understand my heart clearly
I don't understand what you're saying
So please invite Mr. Luong Han Van
Come up and introduce yourself
Show off your talent
And his call for election
Hi everybody
I am
Champion of the junior high school singer contest
Last season
I am
Literature "Spring"
Spring
Pure
I am "Spring" brother
We all have to go
We all go
Good poetry
Thank
So what is your election campaign talent today?
I did see it
Football is on the other side
I haven't played football in many months
Let's dance a few times
Can it warm people up?
Long time no play
So professional
Our young man Tran Tuan Hao
Both are very good players
Thank
So let's see
Next brother
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
What election talent will this day bring?
Dancing all night, of course dancing
One two three
So shy
It is this level
Okay
Next brother
I'm done preparing
Travel to Taiwan somewhere strong
Tour guide please choose
Lazy sheep
I am Lam Hieu Phong
Wait a minute, you're a lazy sheep
Yes, you are
I am the gray wolf
Gray wolf
Because at that time I was mixing the sound for the gray wolf character
Really
So me and lazy sheep
Sing a song together
I want to study now
Can you sing now?
You sing
One
Two
Ba
Yes, that's fine
The lyrics are so clear
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
So talent
Very simple
I myself have a lot of musical instruments
On me
The question is, do you want to listen to this erhu?
Erhu
This Erhu today
It's broken
No, it hasn't been fixed yet
Adjust it a bit
What's different?
Right
Trumpet
Sorry
Some of your brothers
Seems like everyone understands my mistakes every day
Right
Mr. Au Duong Tinh
Hello everyone, my name is Au Duong Tinh
Also the head of the fitness club
I often guide, is it a guide?
Instruct
The usual tour guide is me
Explore with you
Discover
Did you practice the last act?
Definitely not rehearsed
There's no practice
This is called understanding each other
Lately I seem to like complimenting others quite a bit
So I just prepared one
Would you guys guess it was a rap performance?
That's not it
I wrote a poem
Okay, are you ready yet?
It's Taiwanese
So I'm extremely emotional
See this side
Seeing Luong Han Van
Sing a song
Really captivating people
Very fond of people
Ha Thien Hoa
No need to say much more
Does anyone know Mr. Laughing?
Good poetry
Next to him is Lam Hieu Phong
Everyone can leave early today
Next to him there is Au Duong Tinh
Today is definitely not quiet
Good poetry
Okay, today's tour guide position battle
There are three rounds of competition
Guide students to enjoy Dai Dai area
High school fall trip, Teens and Taiwan go together
Okay, let's go
Okay, our first round is
I know this scene
So this round is a test of basic knowledge
About Dai Dai landscape
Dai Dai area's film culture is very popular with everyone
Also attracts people to travel
A huge bright spot
So be a tour guide
It is necessary to be very familiar with these classic scenes
Next
Just look at the next dialogue
What is as soon as the video stops?
After reviewing each question
Listen to my command to raise your hand to answer
Correct answer gets one point
Teacher, what is your command?
What is the teacher's command?
I said, let's start now
Okay
Is there anything a little clearer?
Can I say 3 2 1?
Go to 3 to start
Ha, 1 2 has already begun
Do you want to get off work?
Have
I said let's start
We can get the answer
Is that Okay
Okay
So let's watch the first video
Haven't stopped yet
Haven't started yet
I haven't said 3 2 1 yet
Sorry
Are we ready yet?
Any
Put your hands down first
Okay
Begin
I
The highest
Me first
Teacher
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
Okay, I'll give it
Then I give it to you
He also didn't know what the next sentence was
For him
You will understand better than me
I raised my hand to tell everyone
The two of them definitely know
I don't know
Okay, so I'm 3 2 1
Let's start again
1 started to win replies
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
Okay
Probably
He said
What are you looking at?
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet
Not yet, I remember
I remember that
Just look at what you see
Never seen before
Other people
You speak Cantonese
Speak Cantonese
What are you looking at?
Have you never seen someone else get eliminated?
Okay, so let's see the correct answer
Ta Thien Hoa's memory is really good
Because that day I remember
What are you looking at?
Haven't you seen anyone else being eliminated yet?
It must have been said more than two hundred times
So it's very difficult to forget
When was this movie filmed?
Just ten years ago
Yes, the year 2011
First time filming with Ta Thien Hoa
I find it truly a rare opportunity
I couldn't believe it
That's how everyone will watch it
But I will always exaggerate
The point is not because they miss Lap Thanh
It's because seeing Lap Thanh will remind you of Ta Thien Hoa
For me
It's an experience
Very magical
And also very beautiful, and will always be
Unforgettable
Sorry
Time is up
School's over
Yes, this can be talked about for a long time
The two of them said together
Luong Han Van and I just kept looking
You, Lap Thanh
Do you want to sit with Ta Thien Hoa?
Luong Han Van and I will be better if we sit together
What are you looking at?
Haven't seen anyone else commemorating?
Changing places is not good, the more you talk, the worse it gets
It's miserable
But really thank you Ta Thien Hoa
Actually this time
In "The brother who overcomes all difficulties" golden dictionary
It also counts as a meeting again, right?
Right
So at this meeting
Do you feel any different from before?
At the time of filming, she was still married
And now not only are you married
And he also has two more children
Okay, it's over
Okay, so Mr. Ta Thien Hoa received 1 point
Come on, let's see
Next quiz video
He looked at him
"Condor Hero"
Others don't know
I thought I hit that guy
It's true that I'm sorry for her
Even if you hit me, it's right for me
Even if I beat a pig and a dog, I won't beat you
The next sentence of "If I beat a pig or a dog, I won't beat a guy"
I know
Hoang Dung said
Even if I beat a pig and a dog, I won't beat you
I only fight Hoang Quan Trung
Really amused by him
I know, even if I beat a pig and a dog, I won't beat you
We attack Vien Vinh Nghi
I don't dare continue with this
I know
I beat the pig and the dog, but I won't beat you
I will give you a sideways glance
I know
I also know
Truong Tri Lam immediately looked at Hoang Dung
He hit me
Isn't he heartbroken?
Sweet, she smiled so sweetly
That's probably it
Okay, thank you for Lam Hieu Phong's outstanding performance
But just now is not the correct answer
I beat the pig and the dog, but I won't beat you
Mr. Luong Han Van
Am I not as good as a pig or a dog?
Congratulations Mr. Luong Han Van for answering correctly
Let's watch the exact video, come on
I beat the pig and the dog, but I won't beat you
Are we not as good as pigs and dogs?
Are we not equal to pigs and dogs?
The movie that year was
It will be divided into Taiwanese and Mandarin versions
It's four brothers
That year when you guys were filming
They all use Taiwanese, right?
The vast majority are like that
So you guys have seen it yourself
There are no Mandarin versions of those movies
Few
Just watched this recently
Because I want to study Mandarin diligently
Right
Our competition has ended
Okay
So because teenage high school students
Coming from the Five Lakes and Four Seas
So actually, tour guides are even more needed
Good conversational ability
It's extremely important
Round two of the answer competition
It's "Listen to the pronunciation and guess the content"
Let's watch the video together
I couldn't understand a word
I guess one
3 2 1 come on
Mr. Au Duong Tinh
I knew very quickly
Finish it
Was it Trieu Van Trac just now?
Left
I recognized him very quickly
It's over
Extremely fast closing
Just now you just translated a big idea
Let's see
Do you know the dialogue?
What did you say earlier?
Can you listen again?
Okay, let's listen again
A little louder
I know the last sentence is what I confirmed
Came out a long time ago
The last sentence is correct
What about the previous sentence?
Let me guess
The first two sentences are probably
They are very smart
After eating the meat cake, I rushed out early
Finished eating the meat pie
The meat pie is the important point
Meat pie
Extremely unique
But is it the correct answer?
Very smart
I know
Come on, Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
Those two people's eyes were very bright
As soon as I called them, they immediately rushed out
Thank you Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
But that was not the correct answer
If not, I'll tell you guys
First and last sentences
Then everyone guesses the sentence in the middle
Is that Okay
Okay
The first question is that Teacher Lieu is really good
What a great talent
Earlier, Au Duong Tinh also replied
Last sentence
Immediately rush out
Yes, immediately rush out
Let's look at the sentence in the middle
Teacher Tieu is really good
(I already guessed it), immediately rushed out
Now what I doubt
It's Trieu Van Trac talking nonsense
Second sentence
If not, then simulate it directly
I know
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
Teacher Tieu is really good
It's a bit similar
Right
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
Teacher Tieu is really good
He made it clear
Immediately rushed out
This question may be a bit difficult for us
If not, I will announce the correct answer
After that, no one gets points
Teacher Trieu Van Trac said earlier
Teacher Tieu is really good
So quickly, my sight was restored
Come out already
Visual recovery
Yes, so it's actually quite difficult
I've heard it so many times and still can't figure it out
It's really not simple
The last two rounds were very special
Let's see the next round
"Listen to the rhythm and guess the song"
Everyone knew
A good tour guide for us
A definite elite tour guide
You must know how to sing loudly on the bus, right?
That's right
So the following game
We'll get started
Be careful, take care
Try your best
Now, okay
Can't wait already?
What is this?
Okay, the person who stole the front seat
It's Ta Thien Hoa
You sing
No, let everyone know in advance
Name of this song
This song is so easy
You don't remember
No, usually someone has already closed it
"May of Friendship"
Answer correctly
Sing a few songs
Want to sing?
Now, can we hear Ta Thien Hoa sing?
Struggling in a beautiful dream, each day I risk my life to move forward
Run in the rain and wind, stay drunk without hesitation
All stories seem to begin in the passage of time
Infatuated
Thank
We must tell everyone
One is why I met Thien Hoa
Run out
At that moment, I immediately knew the name of this song
Because normally we often have people who make mistakes
It's "The May of Friendship"
There are also wrong lyrics
Because the first sentence is
I don't remember either
Tell me who this person is
I didn't tell you his last name was Tran
Tran family
I'm curious
There are 2 characters with classic roles here
I want to ask if it's really going to be filmed
Now at the studio, we have 3 hairstyles
Who can
Playing Tran Hao Nam's most classic role
I feel his father's hairstyle
All very similar
But we still have to see the three of them go around
See if the expressions and actions are the same
You can
Does actor Dang Y Kien look like Tran Hao Nam?
Any
Simulation of Tran Hao Nam
We can give a little direction
I feel like maybe this is it
First you have to go through here
Then two people from both sides
Yes, this is fun
This way, there will be that feeling
Move forward
You're so bold
I imagine myself like
The people in there sing together
Sing together
Okay, next person
Okay, let's go home
Come on, Tang Ham Giang
Okay, 3 2 1
Begin
That's right, there is one more move
Tran Hao Nam has a classic move
The most classic move
Come on, Thach Khai
Okay, third person
Looks very serious
Okay
Tran Hao Nam
Yes
Winner
Yes, because he remembers
There is a classic move
Let's see what the next song is
Come on, let's take a look
Mr. Luong Han Van's answer
Red sun
So familiar, right?
Even if fate is fragile
Even if fate is winding and tortuous
Even if destiny is so scary that your life is full of blandness
So don't cry or feel sorry for yourself
Don't give up
I will be with you all my life
All are classic songs
This song is by Mr. Ly Khac Can
Right
Correct
Super cool
Actually, there is a period of time
I don't sing his songs anymore
Because he also sang too much
I remember back in 1989
He participated in the contest "New King of Singing"
Also sing his song "Deep Deep Deep".
I know that song "Deep Deep Deep".
Sing a few songs
Luong Han Van competed in "The King of Singing" in 1989
You said you were faint
Even though it's so painful
I'm helpless and say I'm weak
You said you were faint
Even though it's so painful
The tears on my face have dried
Blow dry two wet tears
While he was singing
Really attractive
Thank
I want to ask something
You guys have each nominated
My other friends
Come join "The brother who overcomes all obstacles".
Actually, we don't really want other people to participate in this
Because we can participate again
Join again
Everyone participates in season 2
Come on, let's take a look
What's the next song?
Any
How fast is that?
Just sing
I can't really say the name of the song
Maybe you can't sing the lyrics at all
But there is 1 rule
That I can sing
Let's start asking for the right to answer again, okay?
Guys, wait a minute
We count 3 2 1 and win
Come on, 3 2 1
Begin
Don't win anymore, I already won
Mr. Luong Han Van won
Come on, let's take a look
What is Mr. Luong Han Van's answer?
"Thien Thien Khuc Ca"
Extremely accurate
Listen to this song
We are together
Comes from the lyrics
Through the far roads I travel
Coming from the stars in the night sky
Brighter than the moon tonight
Not as beautiful as this night
But it doesn't let me enjoy it either
Because today you sing with me
Thank you for Luong Han Van's song
Can you give me half a point?
If only I could sing that rhythm out
I feel it's a bit unfair to me
I feel it's very fair
Actually, Mr. Ta Thien Hoa and Mr. Tran Tieu Xuan
Previously danced together to this song
Is that right?
If not, let's watch the video
We see if everyone can find it
I do remember that
I see
Correct
I still remember what Tran Hue Nhan wore
A pure white dress
At that time the design was all raft jumping
They all kissed Tran Hue Nhan
Then get off stage, right?
That's natural
Benefits of rafting, right?
He feels "The older brother overcomes all difficulties"
The stage can also be designed like that
When Trieu Van Trac finished singing, we were all together
Next time we'll see if we can do it
Actually, before that, Mr. Ta Thien Hoa and Mr. Tran Tieu Xuan
They all do raft jumping
Except for Ms. Tran Hue Nhan
Are you still rafting for anyone else?
Of course there are many
There is principal Dam Vinh Lan
There is also Mai Diem Phuong
Truong Quoc Vinh
Actually, they were all very happy at that time
Their time
Your time is not their time
Yes, at that time they were
Correct
We're the same age
He can go everywhere
Going everywhere to perform with those singers
An extremely dreamy experience
Let's see
What is the next question?
Mr. Luong Han Van excellently came
Do you really understand or are you pretending?
"Unfortunately I'm an Aquarius"
Answer correctly
We play a snippet of the song
I'll be back, don't make me cry
Especially when you know that Aquarius likes tears the most
If it is the sentence after the farewell
Then you can keep your mouth shut
Even though it hurts even more
Thank you for Luong Han Van's song
You guys colluded so of course you knew
Actually, Mr. Luong Han Van and Ms. Duong Thien Quyen
Been friends for many years
So perform in this test
Did she ever tell you?
Didn't say anything special
But last time, he was on stage for the first time
In "Brother's Youth"
I have turned into a "spring" teenager
After that she always laughed at me online
So we talked about that
So you are in her heart
An extremely funny friend
4 brothers
I feel like you guys are really similar
Like younger than your age
Don't dare
Soul age
We all love to play
Do you still have this mask?
I have something to share
A story from the great bay area
Every evening when preparing to go to bed
You will
Turns out you guys are all "mask people"
Because every night
At least 2 people
Will wear a mask
Your skin is very beautiful
Even more beautiful than Thach Khai
Brother, don't cry
There is definitely a road ahead
Don't cry, there will definitely be a way ahead
Let's see
Total results of the previous game
Now we have it
There are no plus points
Didn't get points though
But he got 3 more fans
Thank
So let's congratulate Mr. Luong Han Van
Can be selected in advance
1 in 4 means of transportation
This is very good
Very standard
That's OK
Very good
Why choose D?
Because of travel
Then you just need to spend a little money
Being able to freely go to different places
No need to sit on the bus
With strangers
I also don't want to hear the director "singing".
No need to come either
places that you don't like, are quite free
Okay, thank you Thien Hoa
Any
Choose to lose my D
Why?
You have already chosen
Leave it to our brother Ta Thien Hoa
Read out C first
Off-road bicycles travel freely
straight to the North flank
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa read
Have you all heard and understood?
I understand
Why did you choose C, Ta Thien Hoa?
I feel like a taxi, or a tourist car
All very normal
If you ride your own bike
You will have lots of time
Cycling and admiring the scenery
Enjoy
Enjoy the scenery
Enjoy the atmosphere
New is the meaning of tourism
Next are you two
Can I go first?
Okay
Express buses deliver orchids and pumpkins
That's why I chose it earlier
Read the question again, right?
I read it again
I love rap
Also love the bus
So Mr. Au Duong Tinh chose B
So next here
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong, choose one
Choose 1 of 4
Because it wasn't chosen
But I feel like the private driver has 14 years of experience
quite suitable for me
You watch them
Take a taxi
Taxi
Taxi, bicycle, fast bus or something
Something
While traveling
You will have to shop, you will have to enjoy
If you drive other cars
Where do you go after shopping?
But I'm in my own car
The driver pawned the goods for him
Convenient
That's why I decided to choose me, the leisurely tour guide
Very true, but very lonely
Okay, so the brothers have all made their choices
Next will have to proceed
Extremely good at acting
The next challenge is extremely challenging
ability to understand and express
of 4 tour guide candidates
Need 4 classmates to do the challenge together
Except for the first one
The remaining 3 people must wear noise-canceling headphones
After the first person finishes watching the video
Need to narrate and convey to a second person
Just like that
The last person recites and performs the dialogue
In the end, it was up to the teenagers to vote
Choose the best performer
in the hearts of three modern teenagers
through performance
So specific performance standards
You guys are not professional actors either
So let's see how you're feeling, okay?
Looks very professional
So before our game officially begins
Still have to choose the first person
Send one person
Out of the 4 people, send 1 person there
Pull the hammer and paper away
OK
The loser goes first
Pull hammer and paper
Lose, leave
The first person is Mr. Luong Han Van
He ranked 2nd
I'm second
Pull hammer and paper
I'm 3rd
Before the game officially starts
We ask the remaining 3 brothers to put on their headphones
Bring on the props
Brothers, come on
We stand in a line
1 2 3 4
Now, stand in a line
They can't hear
Now, our challenge officially begins
Come on, Mr. Luong Han Van
Here is an excerpt
in "Martial Arts Extra Story"
Very nice
It's too noisy
I don't hear it
We ourselves did not hear it
What did you say?
I can't hear that one
Okay, come on
Listen again
Do you need a companion?
This person is the counter manager
Look at that look
Forgot to introduce myself
My last name is Hoang, Hoang Thao Khau
Is Thao's family name Hoang, sir?
Southerners, pay attention
Southerners do not clearly distinguish between king and emperor
The word "Hoang" is "gold" in yellow beans
Beans are beans in yellow beans
My name immediately read as Hoang Dau Dau
Alright
Okay, Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
OK, now I'm acting
OK
Do you need a waiter?
This is the counter manager, right?
Look at that look
Still the same person
Forgot to introduce myself
My last name is Hoang, Hoang Thao Khau
Still there? Is it that long?
Is the gangster's name Hoang, sir?
Southerners do not clearly distinguish between emperor and king
This is Hoang
Is the gold in yellow beans
Beans are beans in yellow beans
My name immediately read as Hoang Dau Dau
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong was completely dumbfounded
Okay, Mr. Luong Han Van has finished acting
Can I hold this?
Not allowed
No way, sorry
Pass it on to Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
Do you need a waiter?
This atmosphere is fine
I forgot to introduce myself
My last name is Hoang, Hoang of the Hoang Thao stage
My name is Dau
Beans of beans
Next is Hoang Dau Dau
It's over?
I already remember a lot
Okay, Mr. Lam Hieu Phong finished conveying
Now, next
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa was speechless
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa must convey it to Mr. Au Duong Tinh
Very simple
Check out Ta Thien Hoa's performance
Are you a tonic?
Do you need a waiter?
Very stylish
My name is Hoang
Robber boss
Not
My last name is Hoang, Hoang Thao Khau
My name is Dau
Bean
That's right, Dau
Correct
Hoang Dau Dau, that's right, Hoang Dau Dau
OK
Mr. Au Duong Tinh can perform once
Okay, do it now
Are you a tonic?
Very stylish
He's already started rapping
Found the rhythm
My name is Hoang
Hoang
What?
Bean
Hoang
What?
Bean
No, Dau
It's funny
Hoang Dau Dau
Are not
Bean
Hoang Dau Dau
What a comedy
I do not know
It's extremely great
Do you want to grade each other?
Just now I saw the opponent's performance
I see the scene of Luong Han Van probably
Must go into a store
Yes, go to a store
Go apply
Show them once
Four people can
Let's see this excerpt
OK
Waiter
This is the counter manager
Look at that look
Forgot to introduce myself
My last name is Hoang, Hoang Thao Khau
Is Thao's family name Hoang, sir?
Southerners, pay attention
Southerners do not clearly distinguish between king and emperor
The word "Hoang" is "gold" in yellow beans
Beans are beans in yellow beans
Hoang Dau Dau
Immediately read Hoang Dau Dau
I saw the opponent's performance just now
Do you feel anything?
Extremely cool
So I feel like I am the most standard
That's the entry there
"Are you a tonic?" That sentence is very good
I am passing it on to you
Thank
So next, three teenagers
It's time for your special review
Evaluate
Be careful what you say, boy
I feel like everyone is very good this round
So Thach Khai, who do you vote for?
I exclude
Mr. Luong Han Van is here
Because Mr. Luong Han Van was the first to see it
And I vote one vote for Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
That's right
Tang Ham Giang
Was that look in your eyes just now considering it?
Have you thought about who to vote for yet?
I want to apologize to Lam Hieu Phong
Because Hieu Phong's memory is too good
After watching it once
Actually, I remember it very clearly
In fact, he narrated it
It's almost the same as what Mr. Luong Han Van told me
So I feel
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong performed extremely well just now
I feel like the two of us are so helpless
When he turned around, it was completely different
It's changed
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa, you must know that I am also an actor
When I received that script
I immediately acted in my own way
Got it
Because I have to communicate a little better, I will pass it on
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa just did not perform at all
So what about Tran Tuan Hao?
I feel like I will vote for it
Mr. Au Duong Tinh - the person who brings me a lot of joy
Because in the end I feel for Au Duong Tinh
answering myself
Two people are arguing
I feel extremely happy
Seeing his appearance is extremely adorable
Among them, the most helpless person is Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
I am the most helpless in the middle
Just now after Mr. Lam Hieu Phong finished acting, Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
Can be seen
Still want to remember that line
Want to go perform
But it doesn't give space to develop
This hurdle of mine is quite difficult
But I could see it
Just now, Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
In the dialogue, there are few questions
had an extremely excellent performance
Thank
Of course, Mr. Luong Han Van
It's an actor
Extremely standard
I really cannot comment on this
Yes, all very good
Thank you for the acting of the 4 brothers
So next here
Our challenge game is over
Food selection category
OK
Go to the most favorite section
So the next selection sequence is
Why choose this?
Because you can drive your own car to Hong Kong
There is a place called Tay Cong, eat seafood there
Also visit intangible cultural heritage
Intangible cultural heritage
Great gulf heritage, right
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong thinks extremely carefully
I've already outlined a route to help everyone
So good
Next is Mr. Au Duong Tinh, what do you choose?
Because I'm a "pfox"
Simple idol
I feel in these 4
The most simple thing is the roadside restaurant
Because when I remember going to the roadside restaurant
Except for the food
I will see the whole scene
When we went out to eat together
Must wear sandals
Be sure to wear a tank top and shorts
Extremely comfortable
Roadside restaurant, let's go together
I've seen the nightlife scene
Next is Ta Thien Hoa
Why?
Is quite unique, there are also
A lot of people went there, the atmosphere was very lively
When eating and drinking
The mood suddenly became very happy
Very fun
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa, what's more, the place was packed
So it's definitely not easy to park
He rode his bike, he parked easily
Correct
Only by cycling can you smell that fragrance
Of course
So it's definitely this one
Next is Mr. Luong Han Van
Why?
Because
I need to pay to call a taxi
That restaurant is done
Very prosperous
Just opened a chain of restaurants
Taking a taxi to get there definitely requires navigation
Because you won't go the wrong way
The restaurant is very famous
The restaurant is extremely convenient to get there
After eating, you can go shopping
4 brothers introduced
I like everything
I also feel very good
Next challenge
Will choose the category of accommodation when traveling
You have to keep trying, okay?
OK
Fellow students, I'm finally back
Been waiting for a long time
Let you wait for a long time
Why, where are you going?
Be a tour guide
Originally wanted to take everyone to find out
next travel category
Going to survey?
The result happened on a stormy day
I stopped above everyone's heads
about 2 hours
Just landed
Alright
So now we continue the game
Because I heard that 4 of you study
Previously, I played extremely well
Next here
Finally we talk about out traveling
Eat, drink, sleep
Where to stay
Then it will be this round
To decide where everyone is
The challenge of this round is through building tourist attraction obstacles
Look at the 4 candidates, who can ride a tricycle
through 4 tourist destinations of the great bay area
Lead the group to the finish line fastest
The challenge needs to be conducted in 2 teams of one person
Finally, according to individual time challenges to conduct rankings
Behaviors such as overturning the vehicle, touching the line, and destroying equipment
Each violation will add 5 seconds
Next we would like to invite the contestants
Decide who will be a team with whom
To conduct competition
Then
He will form a team with Thien Hoa
Me and Han Van become a team
Get ready, team one
Departure
Go ahead
Try your best
Now I have surpassed Hieu Phong
Passing the Canton Tower
Han Van's waist strength is good
Unexpectedly, Mr. Hieu Phong used a special method
Mr. Hieu Phong passed directly
Use special methods
Go ahead
Speeding up
Mr. Hieu Phong crossed the Hong Kong-Zhuhai-Macau bridge
Got the egg tart
Give me some space
Must play the flute
Quiet
Mr. Han Van was a bit choked up
There was a cry
Alright
Mr. Han Van is really fast
Went over the speed bump
Come directly
It's over
After Mr. Han Van finished eating the egg cake
Truly full of power
Blow out the sound, let's go
Come on, Mr. Hieu Phong, come on
Come on, come on
No rush
It's so difficult
Come on, Mr. Hieu Phong, come on
Try your best
Heady
Mr. Hieu Phong
You can use your feet
"Enthusiastic people" will give you a push
"Enthusiastic people"
This push is extremely important
Using your feet does not make a mistake
Making a mistake means increasing the time
Yes, first round of competition
Round 1, the two players have completed the competition
I think Han Van rode this bike a lot when he was young
Mr. Han Van
Is this the toy that you still play with to this day?
Extremely skillful
Ride every day, practice every day
Well, next here are two riders
Get ready
Departure
Start super
Begin
Mr. Thien Hoa intended to play dirty
But he couldn't kick Mr. Tinh
Hurry up
I'm here
Mr. Au Duong Tinh is preparing to knock down the "Guangzhou tower".
Careful
Long time no see
No problem
Mr. Thien Hoa quickly honked the horn
Mr. Thien Hoa still has a chance
Mr. Hoa is careful
See who can eat the egg tart faster
Both of them had reached the location to eat the egg tarts
Now is frozen time, unable to move
Blow the flute in each other's faces
You're so naughty
Mr. Thien Hoa is famous
Mr. Tinh went through the speed bump
But it seems like the car's engine has a problem
Mr. Thien Hoa hit him once
Knocked Mr. Tinh off the speed bump
But I'm stuck there
Mr. Au Duong Tinh used his entire front leg
Speed ​​is not divided between high and low
So tired
Anh Thien Hoa attacked unsuccessfully
His expression was extremely drained
Speed ​​is not divided between high and low
Mr. Thien Hoa has obtained an oxygen accelerator
Yes, the destination has been reached
Whoever gets the right to go first in this will win
Correct
Maybe Han Van wins
Mr. Han Van must be very fast
Is that true?
No way, because his legs are too long
Is it stuck?
Show off secretly
After two rounds of challenges have ended
The one who uses the least amount of time is
One minute and five seconds, congratulations to Mr. Han Van
Already given up
Well, here we go next
Travel categories are based on the previous ranking order
And choose in turn
Choose a house to stay in when traveling
You choose first
That's right, you choose first
I will choose
So what should Mr. Hieu Phong do?
Traveling
Because before that he
Called a taxi which was quite cheap
Convenient again
But accommodation is very important
So you must choose a very luxurious place
Should have chosen the hotel
I know
Rest is very important
I think it's so thoughtful
That's right, put your money where it matters most
Yes, luxury hotel
I discovered it as my age increased
Psychology will become smaller and smaller
But there are some people, like our seniors
Whether 60, 70, 80 years old
Everyone can come to our dorm room
That's right
Can feel a little sensation
When I was young
Great
Yes, next one
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
I don't choose D
The most important thing is that it's cheap, it will probably be very cheap
Homestay will have a little more incentives
But it can't be as cheap as yours
Does anyone know why?
Because Hong Kong is a tourist destination
This is Mach Ly Hao trail
It is a world-famous tourist destination
You can see the mountains, you can also see the river
Mr. Hieu Phong
You drove a special vehicle, right?
That's right
He drove that car right into the tent
That tent is his
Normally used to wrap that car
You can also save on parking fees
Car wrap
Four residences have now been selected
Now we will give the right to choose
Delivered into the hands of four members of the youth group
Four young men
Everyone needs to follow suit
The choice of our four brothers
To decide
Whose travel plan do you want to choose the most?
Four brothers
Each person will have 1 minute
To pull votes
That's right, call them to your travel plan
Let me go first
Hello everyone, I am your "Tourism Ambassador".
I am Lam Hieu Phong
It is the elegant and gallant Lam Hieu Phong
Became a "Tourism Ambassador".
Let me introduce
I will personally drive the specialized vehicle
Because I have a license plate from the Hongkong-Zhuhai-Macau area
So you can drive to Macau to eat egg tarts
Everyone watched, everyone else was a bicycle or a bus
Can't go there at all
Other parts of the Greater Bay Area
But if I drive, I can get there
Anywhere in the Greater Bay Area
Yes, thank you for Mr. Hieu Phong's nomination
Yes, next invite Ta Thien Hoa
Yes, you four are handsome
Choose now
Brother, no need to say anymore, I choose you
I am a hot new tour guide recently
I have helped you
Arrange your schedule in a very special way
It is
Each of us has a bicycle
This is not a simple bike
It is the most popular bicycle today
It's super light
The only thing I'm worried about is that your car is that car
It's the kind that pedals like you're not pedaling at all
The path we take will be an extremely bright one
People can stop at any time
See the sights and chat
Then continue on to that unique restaurant
Why do I call it a unique restaurant?
Could be things like
For example, you can watch this belly dance
That's right
I'm full
After cycling all day
Feeling a bit tired
We have arranged a unique homestay
Feel the love of the locals
It is a trip full of poetry and extremely refreshing
Well, next
Mr. Tinh
It's the next person
The bus is nothing special
I feel it's important that we go together
I'm with you guys, right?
And the second thing, what to eat
Roadside shop
And the main place to stay is the dorm room
Just like where we are now
Dormitory of "Brother who overcomes all difficulties"
Despite everyone's age
They are no longer young
So I feel that the simple tour guide is me
But I'll go explore with you, thank you
I won't say it, but I'll say I'm excited
Yes, next invite Mr. Han Van
Hi everybody
Let me introduce myself
I am a very popular and hot tour guide
Don't imitate me
Why am I hot?
Because I'm the best singer
So in that taxi
I can just chat with people
Singing for everyone to hear
And you will get to choose that luxury hotel
Because we need to enjoy and eat something special
Then our taxi
Can be located
And we can go eat
Then go shopping, extremely convenient
Great
Well, now you four
If you want to go with any tour group
Then stand behind him, let's go
Welcome
Year
Four
Ba
Two
One
Please turn around
Every young person
I have chosen a method of travel that I like best
So our golden brand tour group
Officially established
Next here
We will follow together
Golden brand tour group
Let's go to the Great Bay Area together
To experience world-class cities
Brings us the vitality of youth
Night at Big Bay, waiting for you to experience
Welcome everyone to "Youth School" to attend
Graduation ceremony
Hobbies that I like and are passionate about
Can become your job
Not everyone can be like that
Even though when you start studying you don't like it
But in the process
You can find joy
When the seeds of new love bloom
When school ended, I kept sneaking around
Follow along
Who can win the honor?
Become a graduate of the youth school
Be spoiled
Make char siu
It's so difficult
This is so difficult
How come?
The final battle
It hurts so much
Everyone watch
Please invite all of my brothers
Youth school
Go on stage together
They've all arrived